<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Union for Nubian Studies</title>
    <link>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Union for Nubian Studies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dotawo</title>
      <link>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/dotawo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/dotawo/</guid>
      <description>Dotawo offers a platform in which the old meets the new, in which archaeological, papyrological, and philological research into Meroitic, Old Nubian, Coptic, Greek, and Arabic sources confront current investigations in modern anthropology and ethnography, Nilo-Saharan linguistics, and critical and theoretical approaches present in post-colonial and African studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medieval Nubia Wiki</title>
      <link>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/wiki/</guid>
      <description>The Medieval Nubia Wiki is dedicated to the collaborative publication of scholarly resources for the study of medieval Nubia. It is a site that will grow as scholars from the international community use and contribute to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medieval Sai Project</title>
      <link>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/sai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/sai/</guid>
      <description>The Medieval Sai Project is the blog written by Alexandros Tsakos (along with occasional guest authors), where there are published views and news from the world of Sudan Archaeology and Nubian Studies with a special focus on Medieval Nubia, the period between ca the 5th and the 15th centuries CE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory of the World / Nubia</title>
      <link>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/motw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/motw/</guid>
      <description>The Nubia public library hosted at the Memory of the World is a repository of books pertaining to the field of Nubiology maintained by the Anarchist Nubiology Squad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meroe Archival Project</title>
      <link>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/meroe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/meroe/</guid>
      <description>The Meroe Archival Project (MAP) re-examines Peter L. Shinnie’s domestic excavations at the Royal City of Meroe in order to:
 provide research exchanges and training between University of Reading and the University of Khartoum; produce a more refined understanding of diachronic change, economic and social life at Meroe; capture the memories of those who took part in these critical excavations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NubiaFEST</title>
      <link>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/nubiafest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/nubiafest/</guid>
      <description>NubiaFEST is an annual open online festival organized by the Union for Nubian Studies and The Nubia Initiative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nubian Image Archive</title>
      <link>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.unionfornubianstudies.org/projects/flickr/</guid>
      <description>The Nubian Image Archive is a public domain repository on Flickr for historical and contemporary images of Nubia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
